<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blender &#8211; Courses</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/Course_wordpress/course-tag/blender/feed/?simply_static_page=999" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://sanketl0.github.io/Course_wordpress</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:56:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Complete Blender Creator, 3D Modelling</title>
		<link>https://sanketl0.github.io/Course_wordpress/courses/complete-blender-creator-learn-3d-modelling-for-beginners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mhtechin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.themeum.com/wordpress/edumax/?post_type=course&#038;p=205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Learn how to create 3D Models and Assets for games using Blender, the free-to-use 3D production suite. We start super simple so you'll be ok with little or no experience. With our online tutorials, you'll be amazed what you can achieve.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Are you new to PHP or need a refresher?</strong> Then this course will help you get all the fundamentals of Procedural PHP, Object Oriented PHP, MYSQLi and ending the course by building a CMS system similar to WordPress, Joomla or Drupal.<br />
<strong>Knowing PHP has allowed me to make enough money to stay home and make courses like this one for students all over the world.</strong> Being a PHP developer can allow anyone to make really good money online and offline, developing dynamic applications.<br />
Knowing <strong>PHP </strong>will allow you to build web applications, websites or Content Management systems, like WordPress, Facebook, Twitter or even Google.<br />
<strong>There is no limit to what you can do with this knowledge.</strong> PHP is one of the most important web programming languages to learn, and knowing it, will give you <strong>SUPER POWERS</strong> in the web development world and job market place.<br />
<strong>Why?</strong><br />
Because Millions of websites and applications (the majority) use PHP. You can find a job anywhere or even work on your own, online and in places like freelancer or Odesk. You can definitely make a substantial income once you learn it.<br />
<strong>I will not bore you <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong><br />
I take my courses very seriously but at the same time I try to make it fun since I know how difficult learning from an instructor with a monotone voice or boring attitude is. This course is fun, and when you need some energy to keep going, you will get it from me.<br />
<strong>My Approach</strong><br />
Practice, practice and more practice. Every section inside this course has a practice lecture at the end, reinforcing everything with went over in the lectures. I also created a small application the you will be able to download to help you practice PHP. To top it off, we will build and awesome CMS like WordPress, Joomla or Drupal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
